Well after the disappointing take down of Crackmes.de I took it upon myself to mirror the crackmes (thanks for the inspiration @darelgrif) as well as the solutions that were on that site. Please find the following linked zip that contains almost 1000 crackme’s for all levels. Please enjoy and mirror/spread.

Nothing disappears once it’s been posted on the internet. If your curious how I did this python and urllib2 scraped the links from a popular archiving site. Enjoy!

malwareninja